bagsok.com 2011-11-24

# Privacy Policy - BagsOK: Fashion Handbags, Discount Leather Bags Online Shop

Bagsok recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personal and financial information. We have instituted reasonable policies and security measures to protect the information you provide for us. When you register online with Bagsok or use our online store you give us your consent to process and use such submitted personal data in accordance with this privacy policy.  
This privacy policy applies to all protected personal information collected, maintained or used by Bagsok.

**What Information Bagsok Collects**

Bagsok collects personal data from visitors to the website who register their information or who use the online store. We also use cookies (as described below) and track IP addresses so that we can improve our services and enhance your Bagsok experience. In addition, Bagsok collects some protected personal information (e.g., name, address, telephone number(s), credit card information, email address, etc.) from our affiliated companies and, on occasion, from unrelated third parties. To serve you better, we may combine information you give us with other information which is publicly available.

**How Bagsok Uses Information You Provide**

If you give us your personal information, then with your consent, Bagsok will use this information to keep you informed of our special events or promotions, to register you with our website, to administer our website services, and/or to process any orders you may place online. Otherwise, we may use the information you provide for us only to review our performance and to improve our services, or to communicate with you about your order if you have placed one on our site.  
We will send you announcements or communications by email only if you give us your permission to do so by giving the appropriate consent on our web site.  
 ** **

**Does Bagsok Share Your Information With Others?**

Bagsok does not sell, rent or disclose our client's names, addresses, email addresses or other personal information to any non-Bagsok entity. Bagsok may share customer information within Bagsok Group, so that you may be informed of other products that may be of interest to you. Further, in order to maintain our website, to manage our database, to distribute e-mails and to provide client communications, Bagsok contracts with selected third parties. As necessary, the personal information you offer to us may be processed by these third parties, solely on Bagsok’s behalf but we do not authorize any of these service providers to make any other use of your information. We do not otherwise disclose your information to third parties, unless we are required to do so by law or in connection with a legal claim or proceeding. If Bagsok is acquired by another entity or is merged or consolidated, information about Bagsok customers may be made available to the new entity. However, the new entity will agree to protect the confidentiality of your personal information consistent with this Privacy Policy.  
 ** **

**Accuracy and Retention**

You are entitled to request access to and correction of all personal data you provide us, or to remove your name from the Bagsok’s marketing list at any time by contacting our customer service or by contacting us at the email: service@bagsok.com  
 ** **

**About Cookies**

Cookies are pieces of information a web site can send to your computer's browser for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to ascertain which web pages are visited and how often, to make our web site more friendly, and to give you a better experience when you return to the website. For example, cookies allow us to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it every time you visit our site. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you do not have to accept them and you are allowed to disable them. However, your visit to our website will be significantly enhanced if cookies are not disabled. If you do not disable your cookies, you accept our collection and storage of any of your personal information such as cookies contain.  
 ** **

**Acceptance of Privacy Policy and Modifications**

By accessing and using the Bagsok website, you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your information as described in this privacy policy. Bagsok reserves the right occasionally to make changes to our privacy policy or practices. We will post the updated policy on our website, and thus we encourage you to review this page from time to time, particularly each time you use our online shop.

**Contact Us**

If you have any comments or queries regarding our privacy policy, please send an email to [service@bagsok.com](mailto:service@bagsok.com).
